400 pesos per month life insurance with
critical illness
is
25 years old female and non-smoker this
is Sun Life ashore perfect for those
Guston on temporary coverage with
minimal budget this is pure guaranteed
health or life insurance only no
investment you pay as long as you leave
if my diagnosis critical illness the
NASA 36 illnesses list of the policy
until age 70. this plan renews
automatically every five years means
every five years increase an amount to
be paid now minimal payment you are
insured with big amount of coverage
if he's still alive after five years
till age 70 no savings component and no
money back so every five years naging
Christian annual payment and then guide
Shah until 70 years old so from 25 years
old to 70 years old is 45 years to pay
and total payment is 470
350.
guaranteed big coverage in the event of
untimely death not insured which is 500
000 on the spot IB biggest family
choose Sun fit and will Advantage 20. so
this is 20 years to pay if fifteen
thousand seven hundred seventy five
every year
315 500 pesos same coverage now 500 000
select assure Peru this time 114
critical illness and covered
illness
choose life assure if Gusto moyong long
term with cashback choose Sun fitness
advantage you will save 154
850. if you have any question I have a
comprehensive explanation about sunfit
and will just PM me